icanseek.com 2004-06-30

# Everyone.net

  Agreements > Privacy Policy  

  If you have questions or concerns regarding this Policy, you should first contact Everyone.net.

  Everyone.net™ Incorporated ("Everyone.net") has the following Privacy Policy with respect to information gathered on Web pages hosted by Everyone.net ("Service Pages"). Such information is received by both Everyone.net and the owner of the Web site through which you may have requested Everyone.net services (the "Client"). You should contact the Client to determine the privacy policy, if any, that applies to the Client's collection and use of such information. However, in no event shall Everyone.net be liable for the Client's use or disclosure of such information.

  The terms "we" and "us" refer to Everyone.net.

  **The Information We Collect**

  This notice applies to all information collected on the Everyone.net Web site or submitted to Everyone.net at any time through any Service Pages.

Personally Identifiable Information-When visiting Everyone.net's or any Client's Web site and signing up for or using Everyone.net services through any Service Page, you may choose to supply Everyone.net with information that identifies you personally. For **End-Users** , this information may include your name and contact information, gender, birth date, occupation and industry, shipping and billing information, credit card numbers and other payment information, behavior patterns, purchase history, and other information. For **Clients** , this information may include the Client's name and contact information, the Client's Web site information (name, URL, visitors per day, page views per month, description, categorization), payment information (check payee, SSN/Tax ID, bank information), and user comments. We also collect **prospect information** from our End-Users, which may include name and contact information of individual(s) you think would be interested in our services.

  Aggregate Information—We collect non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our Web site and services, and share the aggregate data with advertisers and other third parties.

  Each of Everyone.net's Clients has access to information specific only to that Client's site(s). Each Client will determine what it will do with the collected information; however, each Client has individually agreed to abide by this Privacy Policy and the Everyone.net End-User Agreement.

  **Collection of Personal Information from Children under Thirteen**

  Everyone.net does not allow children known to be under the age of thirteen (13) to register for our services. We may momentarily capture personally identifiable information for purposes of determining whether a user is over the age of thirteen (13) and thus qualifies to use our services. Where the user is under the age of thirteen (13), such information is automatically deleted.

  **The Way We Use Information**

  We use the information you provide about yourself or others to complete the transaction for which the information is intended. Such transactions may include: administering a service, such as email, search, community, advertising sales, ecommerce; completing an order; shipping a product; replying to support requests; or contacting you if you have granted us permission to do so. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy and the End-User Agreement, we do not share this information with outside parties without your permission except to the extent that is necessary to administer the services we offer our Clients and End-Users or to comply in responding to subpoenas, court orders or other legal proceedings.

  From time to time, we also use the information you provide about yourself or others to inform you of additions or improvements to the Everyone.net services as well as conduct member surveys in order to improve our services. These communications will only be sent to the administrative account. 

Through our Everyone Benefits program customers can receive information about third party services that are likely to be of interest. Users of our free service will initial be opted in to this program while customers signing up any of our paid service can choose to opt in. Customers can opt out of our Everyone Benefits program by clicking on the link provided in the email or by visiting our site and opting out.

We may also use personally identifiable End-User information to provide targeted content and commerce opportunities to End-Users based on their demographic and behavioral information.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways or for reasons unrelated to the ones described above without also providing an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

  **Our Commitment to Data Security**

  To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures reasonably designed to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

We use SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption to secure personal identification. In addition, personnel who have access to our database are trained to maintain and secure all information.

   **How You Can Access or Update Your Information**

  **Clients** can access their personally identifiable information that Everyone.net collects online and maintains by logging in to their password-protected (SSL encrypted) Control Center account at [http://www.everyone.net](http://www.everyone.net/) and selecting "Edit My Profile." **End-Users** can access their information by logging in to their password-protected End-User account and selecting to update their "Personal Info." End-Users and Clients can also correct factual errors in their personally identifiable information by sending us a written request that credibly documents and explains the error.

If you have submitted information on our site but do not currently have an account with us, you can access and correct the information that we collect and maintain by contacting us and requesting such information or correction.

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to your information.

  **How to Contact Us**

  Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please contact us online or via postal mail: 2216 O'Toole Avenue, San Jose, CA 95131-1326.

  **Email, Search, and Community Specific Terms and Conditions**

  Everyone.net considers email transmitted via our service to be private correspondence between the sender and recipient. Therefore, we will not monitor, edit or disclose the contents of your private communications, except for reasons provided for in the End-User Agreement.

  Content posted to public community areas is publicly available, and Everyone.net reserves the right to remove any publicly posted content that it deems to be objectionable.

  **Advertising Sales Specific Terms and Conditions**

  We use third-party advertising companies to serve our ads on our Web site. These third-party advertising companies employ cookie and 1x1 pixel . gifs or web beacons to measure and improve the effectiveness of ads for their clients. To do so, these companies may use anonymous information about your visits to our website and other websites. This information can include: date/time of banner ad shown, the banner ad that was shown, their cookie, the IP address. This information can also be used for online preference marketing purposes.

If you want to prevent a third-party advertiser from collecting data, currently you may either visit each ad network's web site individually and opt out or visit the NAI gateway opt-out site to opt-out of all network advertising cookies. [Click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp) for the NAI gateway opt-out site. This site will also allow you to review the third-party advertising companies' privacy policies.

  For more information on how Accipiter manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on our network, please visit <http://www.accipiter.com/about/privacy.php>. For more information on how DoubleClick manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on our network, please visit <http://www.doubleclick.com/us/about_doubleclick/privacy/>. For more information on how Advertising.com manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on our network, please visit <http://www.advertising.com/Privacy.html>.
